https://www.babybjorn.com/user-terms-conditions/

Our online shop is open around the clock as usual, but you may experience slightly longer processing and delivery times due to disruptions in postal services. We have now also extended our return policy to 30 days. Close
Search BabyBjörn for products, colors and materials
Product Categories
Baby Carriers
Baby Bouncers
Travel Crib
Kitchen
Bathroom
No results
User Terms and Conditions
These user terms and conditions govern your use of BabyBjörn AB’s (“BabyBjörn“) website and any social media that BabyBjörn uses, such as Facebook, Twitter and Instagram, (below jointly referred to as the “Website”), and any agreement you may conclude with BabyBjörn via the Website. The Website comprises all information on this website and other websites belonging to BabyBjörn to which the Website provides links, including data files, written text, photographs, videos, other images and marketing material.
BabyBjörn is entitled at any time to make amendments to these terms and conditions as it sees fit without specific notice in advance. When BabyBjörn amends these terms and conditions, BabyBjörn will make the new terms and conditions available on the Website. By using the Website, you accept these user terms and conditions. If you do not accept these terms and conditions, you must not use the Website.
COLLECTING INFORMATION
BabyBjörn values the trust you place in us and recognizes the need for appropriate protection and management of the personal information you share with us. This privacy policy is designed to explain what information we may collect, how we use this information and the choices you have regarding the use and retention of this information.
BabyBjörn gathers customer information as needed to provide service, communicate offers on merchandise and services which we believe will be of interest to you and to administer our business. When you purchase or order a product, subscribe to our newsletter or a service we provide, we may request information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address and credit card information. In addition, our web server will automatically gather information about your visit to our site, such as your browser type, what pages have been viewed, the time of visit, etc. You may access, update or delete any personal information you submit to the web site by contacting us using any of the contact points listed at the bottom of this privacy statement. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.
CONFIDENTIALITY & PERSONAL DATA
BabyBjörn will handle all personal data with safe and secure standards, such as name, address and date of birth, that you provide to BabyBjörn, or that BabyBjörn gains access to as a result of purchase, registration of products purchased, submission of product ratings and reviews, when you participate in competitions or sign up for newsletters. By providing your personal data, you give your consent to BabyBjörn’s use of the data gathered to meet BabyBjörn’s obligations towards you, and to provide you with the service you expect. This may include: delivering the goods you have ordered, performing customer service, to get in contact with you in the event of any problem with delivery or products, carrying out a credit check, use ratings, reviews and comments on other websites (both BabyBjörn’s Website and others’ websites) where BabyBjörn’s products are marketed and sold, sending information about BabyBjörn, and other offers for marketing purposes. The information will only be used within the BabyBjörn Group and by distributors and suppliers that BabyBjörn uses to provide its services, i.e. suppliers that handle the information on behalf of BabyBjörn. These suppliers will only handle information required to perform their services on behalf of BabyBjörn and are obliged by contract to keep the information confidential. The information will not be disclosed to any other third party, i.e. BabyBjörn will not sell the information to anyone. BabyBjörn monitors and processes your personal data in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.
BabyBjörn is the controller of and responsible for the personal data you disclose to BabyBjörn under the Swedish Data Protection Act (1998:204) and the EU Directive 95/46/EC. Your personal data is stored in Sweden and processed within the BabyBjörn Group, in a few cases outside the EEA-area. Personal data will only be transferred outside the EEA-area if the third country either has accepted the Convention for the protection of individuals with regard to automatic processing of personal data or ensures an adequate level of protection.
You can request access to your personal data at: care@babybjorn.com. You have the right to request information about the personal data BabyBjörn holds about you. If your data is incorrect, incomplete or irrelevant, you can request that the information is corrected or removed. Annually, you have the right to request written documentation on the personal information BabyBjörn holds about you. Such request must be in writing and signed by you.
TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES & COOKIES
Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by BabyBjörn and our marketing partners, affiliates, analytics and online customer support providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.
Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.
BabyBjörn uses persistent cookies inter alia to store information on your choice of country the first time you visit the Website. This avoids the need to choose a country each time you visit the Website and also enables you to see prices in your local currency. The cookies also enable BabyBjörn to see whether you have visited the Website before, and which of BabyBjörn’s pages you have visited. Session cookies are used to enhance your experience of the Website.
BabyBjörn uses third-party cookies to collect statistics in analysis tools such as Google Analytics and to market relevant products.
ANALYTICS / LOG FILES
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.
BEHAVIORAL TARGETING / RE-TARGETING
We partner with third-parties to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.
WHAT DOES BABYBJÖRN DO WITH ALL OF THIS INFORMATION?
The information you provide is used by us to provide you with a requested service, such as our online newsletter. It may also be used to notify you of new products, events, and limited time offers with online and local retail partners. We will never share your information with third parties unless as disclosed in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
You may receive periodic mailings from us on new products, services and limited time offers if you have provided us with your mailing address. However, you may opt out of these mailings simply by contacting BabyBjörn by phone or email or writing to us at our mailing address.
BabyBjörn may contact you by phone regarding previous orders placed by you, information or services you've requested. We may also contact you regarding upcoming events, sales, or new product introduction that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive phone contact from us, please let us know by contacting us by phone, email or in writing to our mailing address. Please note, that BabyBjörn will not share, rent or sell your telephone number to any other company or organization.
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web sites.
EMAIL
At BabyBjörn, we do not share your email address with other companies or organizations. However, your email address may be used internally to conduct business including confirming orders, answering questions, provide our newsletter as requested, and other customer related services. You may choose to opt out of receiving news and information by email simply by contacting us by email, phone or in writing. In such instances, you will continue to receive email contact pertaining to any current or outstanding order you have with us.
CONTENT
It is BabyBjörn’s aim that the content of the Website and the information given on it should be up-to-date and accurate. However, it is possible that some information on the Website may be inaccurate. BabyBjörn therefore accepts no liability for any typographical or printing errors, or any information on the Website that is not up-to-date.
In addition to these terms and conditions, BabyBjörn’s terms of sale applies for any purchase and sale of products in BabyBjörn’s online store, which are available in the online store.
BabyBjörn’s products are also sold by retailers who are independent of BabyBjörn. The recommended retail prices listed on the Website are merely recommended retail prices. The retailers set their own prices and have their own terms and conditions. BabyBjörn cannot therefore influence the actual price offered by your nearest retailer. Prices may therefore vary from one retailer to another. The retailers themselves decide the range of products they sell. BabyBjörn cannot therefore influence or guarantee that the products presented on the Website are actually available at your nearest retailer.
COLORS
BabyBjörn cannot guarantee that the colors shown on the Website are an exact representation of the actual colors of the products. The way colors are shown on-screen depends, among others, on your computer settings.
LINKS
The Website may display links to other websites that do not belong to BabyBjörn and are not under BabyBjörn’s control. BabyBjörn accepts no responsibility for protection of privacy or the content of those websites; BabyBjörn displays the links to help visitors to the Website to find more information on specific topics. These websites have their own separate terms and conditions as well as privacy policies.
The Website has a catalogue containing the contact details of BabyBjörn retailers. The retailers are independent of BabyBjörn. The catalogue is provided as a service to you, so that you can contact a nearby retailer.
DATA RETENTION
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at care@babybjorn.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
MATERIAL THAT YOU UPLOAD OR SEND TO BABYBJÖRN
By sending material to BabyBjörn or uploading material to the Website, e.g., text, photographs, videos and other images, you grant BabyBjörn a non-exclusive license itself or via another party without limitation and using all technologies and media, and in all forms, to use the material throughout the world. You also accept that BabyBjörn may alter and edit the material so that it can be used as BabyBjörn considers appropriate. You may revoke this license at any time by notifying BabyBjörn of this. When you revoke the license, BabyBjörn must stop using the material as soon as possible, and not later than within six months. However, BabyBjörn is under no obligation to recall material that has already been distributed.
You may only send material to BabyBjörn to which you are entitled. By sending the material to BabyBjörn, you confirm to BabyBjörn that you are entitled to grant BabyBjörn the license in accordance with the preceding paragraph, that BabyBjörn has no liability for the material that you have sent, and that you will hold BabyBjörn harmless and compensate BabyBjörn for all loss, injury or damage that BabyBjörn may incur as a result of its use of the material, provided that BabyBjörn uses the material in accordance with the above license.
TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHT & INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS
The trade marks, product names, other distinctive marks, designs and domain names used on the Website belong to BabyBjörn, whether or not they are registered. The contents of the Website are protected by copyright and belong to BabyBjörn or are licensed by BabyBjörn.
You must not download, save to your computer or use material from the Website unless you have received BabyBjörn’s written permission, or it is stated on the Website that the material may be downloaded and used in a given manner.
LIABILITY
Notwithstanding anything contained herein to the contrary BabyBjörn accepts no liability towards you for any loss, injury or damage, except in cases where the company’s liability insurance covers the damage, and provided that, where applicable, the insurer accepts that payment be made, and such payment is actually made.
BabyBjörn is never liable for indirect damage, loss of income and other consequential loss or damage of any kind.
FORCE MAJEURE
In the event of force majeure, performance by BabyBjörn of its obligations is postponed. If the period during which force majeure prevails is longer than two months, you and BabyBjörn are both entitled to cancel the agreement you concluded with BabyBjörn via the Website, without thereby incurring any obligation for BabyBjörn to pay damages.
Force majeure means all circumstances beyond BabyBjörn’s control including strikes, staff illness, transport disruption, fire, flood, earthquake, storm, hurricane or other natural disaster, import/export ban, whether this affects the company or its suppliers.
CONTACT INFORMATION
BabyBjorn Inc.
